<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on STEM Notes</title>
    <link>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on STEM Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Jupyter</title>
      <link>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>Installing Jupyter Jupyter requires a prequisite of either Python version 2.7 or version 3.3 and greater.
The recommended installation method is to use the Anaconda distribution which will install Python and Jupyter.
Running Jupyter Notebook Run the following command to run Jupyter Notebook
jupyter notebook Installing JupyterLab JupyterLab is the next-generation web-based user interface for Project Jupyter.
JupyterLab can be installed using either conda, pip or, pipenv.
conda conda install -c conda-forge jupyterlab pip pip install jupyterlab pipenv pipenv install jupyterlab pipenv shell Running JupyterLab JupyterLab can be run with the following command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Framework</title>
      <link>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/hugo/</guid>
      <description>Installing Hugo First of all you will need to setup a Hugo site. You can follow the Hugo Quick Start Guide for that.
The next step is to install a theme. Instructions for doing so can be found in the Hugo themes documentation.
A list of all available themes can be browsed here.
The theme I have chosen to use for this website is cloned from: achary/engimo
Installing a Theme There are two different ways you can install Engimo as a theme:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NodeJS and NPM</title>
      <link>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/node-npm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stem-notes.netlify.com/docs/node-npm/</guid>
      <description>NodeJS is an asyncronous event driven JavaScript runtime built on Chrome&amp;rsquo;s V8 JavaScript engine and comes with its own preinstalled package manager called npm.
Node Package Manager (NPM) is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest software registry, with approximately 3 billion downloads per week. npm opens up an entire world of JavaScript talent to you and to your team. The registry contains over 600,000 packages (building blocks of code).
Open-source developers from every continent share and borrow packages through npm, accessing algorithms designed across the planet or across the street.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>